ACTWU's Department of Occupational Safety and Health Records 5619/015
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
ACTWU's Department of Occupational Safety and Health Records
1934-2001
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America. Department of Occupational Safety and Health
Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers' Union. Department of Occupational Safety and Health
5619/015
110.5 cubic feet
110.5 linear ft.
Correspondence, reports, publications.
This collection consists of correspondence, reports, standards, protocols, OSHA case files, and other files regarding industrial hazards in the textile industry compiled by the Department of Occupational Safety and Health of the Textile Workers Union of America and the Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union. Some of the materials date from after the ACTWU merger with the International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union (ILGWU), these records are scattered throughout the collection and could not be easily separated out to be placed in the related UNITE collection, 6000/019, and was left in place. Industrial hazards featured in this collection include brown lung (byssinosis), carcinogens, asbestos, formaldehyde, vinyl chloride, among others.
6791848
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff
Date completed:
December 2010
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, February 2011
Biographical / Historical
The Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America, the most significant union representing workers in the men's clothing industry, was founded in New York City in 1914 as a breakaway movement from the United Garment Workers. Radical and immigrant workers in the tailors' and cutters' locals were the core of the seceding group, which advocated industrial unionism and economic strikes in opposition to the UGW's craft organization, which they saw as conservative and timid. Their diverging views had come to the fore during the historic 1910 dispute at the Chicago firm Hart, Schaffner, and Marx. The opposition called the strike against the UGW leadership's advice, and reached a path-breaking agreement with management that established an arbitration system to settle disputes.
Members flocked to the new union. Around 50,000 strong at its founding, by 1920 the ACWA counted about 170,000 members. Initially composed mostly of immigrants of Jewish European descent with Socialist leanings, the ACWA quickly welcomed members of a great number of nationalities and diverse backgrounds. Like in other garment unions, most workers and many members were women, but the leadership was predominantly male, a situation that did not change for many decades. Early on the union adopted a centralized administrative structure combined with industrial unionism, with the joint boards' by-laws having precedence over those of locals.
Espousing a philosophy perhaps brought over by its early immigrant socialist members, the Amalgamated went beyond bread and butter issues and adopted a distinctive form of social unionism that was largely absent in the American labor movement. Starting in the 1920s, it provided educational opportunities and recreational facilities for its members, as well as services such as an insurance plan, banks offering personal loans at low interest rates, low-cost housing cooperatives, medical clinics, and even union-owned restaurants.
Sidney Hillman was the first president of the new union and the most important officer in its history. He applied his experience as bargaining representative in Chicago to the whole industry. Under his leadership the union made significant strides in securing better wages and working conditions for its members, and at the same time it consolidated gains and provided stability to the industry through the widespread adoption of the arbitration system tested at Hart, Schaffner, and Marx. Hillman paid close attention to industry issues, such as production, pricing, and marketing. In order to help management meet the competition of non-union firms, the union conducted studies of efficiency, work methods, and factory costs. Letters to the official publication of the union, Advance, document the controversy that ensued within the union over what was perceived to be collaboration with management.
Hillman also understood the importance of labor's involvement in national affairs and political action. In the 1920s the ACWA sent delegates to the Conference for Progressive Political Action and to the Farmer-labor party conventions. Although many members and officers were Socialists, the union stopped short of officially endorsing the party. Communist attempts at gaining influence within the union were firmly curbed. Hillman's participation in national affairs and politics became prominent during the New Deal, when he became a close advisor to Franklin D. Roosevelt on labor and economic issues. He also served on the board of the National Recovery Administration. Later, during World War II, he helped establish the Labor's Non Partisan League. He was also named associate director of the Office of Production Management, which assisted in mobilizing the nation's resources for the war effort. Hillman's prestige perhaps reflected the healthy condition of his union, which by the end of the conflict was strong and stable.
During the post World War II period the union faced a number of significant challenges. Membership continued to grow (peaking at 395,000 in 1968), but the union's political influence and visibility in national affairs declined. In their never ending pursuit of lower production costs, many firms relocated to the South, forcing the union to engage in large organizing efforts. Simultaneously, signs began to appear of changes that would lead to the almost complete demise of the domestic apparel industry and, ultimately, to the erosion of union membership. Foreign imports of cheap clothing goods steadily grew in the 1950s and 1960s, and mushroomed in the following two decades, plunging employment in the apparel sector into a steady decline. Union efforts to stem the tide included Buy American campaigns and extensive lobbying in Congress, but they were to no avail. In 1976, the ACWA merged with the Textile Workers of America to become the Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union. Despite successful and much publicized nationwide actions such as the Farah boycott and the J.P. Stevens corporate campaign, the woes threatening the union's existence continued unabated. The fate of the domestic industry was sealed in the late 1970s and the 1980s by the flight of firms chasing tax breaks and cheap labor abroad. By 1995, when ACTWU voted to merge with the International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union, their combined membership was 350,000. The new Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees (UNITE!) seemed poised to infuse new life in a troubled union.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related collections: 5619: Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America All other 5619 collections and 6000/019: UNITE's Department of Occupational Safety and Health Records
Laundry workers--Labor unions; Textile workers--Labor unions; Clothing workers--Labor unions; Industrial safety; Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers' Union; Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers' Union --Archives; Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America --Archives; Textile Workers' Union of America --Archives; Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers' Union. Department of Occupational Safety and Health--Archives; United States. Occupational Safety and Health Administration.; Textile Workers' Union of America. Department of Occupational Safety and Health--Archives; Laundry, Dry Cleaning, and Dye House Workers International Union --Archives; Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees --Archives; UNITE HERE (Organization) --Archives
6791848
- Dupont Co. Repauno Plant., 1979-1981 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  Scope and Contents
  Gobbstown, New Jersey
- Occupational Safety & Health Review. Dupont. Chemical Workers Association, 1979-1987 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Dupont, 1980-1986 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Safety & Medical Information, 1980-1986 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Safety & Health Administration. Dupont. Deepwater. Texaco. Mobil [1 of 2], 1978-1986 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Safety & Health Administration. Dupont. Deepwater. Texaco. Mobil [2 of 2], 1978-1986 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Dupont Health & Safety, 1981-1987 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- U.S. Dept. of Labor Occupational & Safety (Box 1, Folder 8)
- US Dept of Labor & Occupational Safety, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Rose Marie Meierer. Transcript 1 [1 of 2], 1984 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Rose Marie Meierer. Transcript 1 [2 of 2], 1984 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Rose Marie Meierer. Transcript 2 [1 of 2], 1984 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Rose Marie Meierer. Transcript 2 [2 of 2], 1984 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Rose Marie Meierer. Transcript 3 [1 of 2], 1984 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Rose Marie Meierer. Transcript 3 [2 of 2], 1984 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Celanese Corp., 1973-1980 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  Rockhill, S.C.
- Celanese Corp, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  Rock Hill, S.C.
- Cone Mills., 1980-1983 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  Greensboro, NC
- Chase Bag Co., 1980 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  Dallas, TX
- Cone Mills, 1980-1983 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Cone Mills. Granite Finishing, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  Haw River, NC
- Cone Mills, 1975-1981 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  Reidville, NC
- Cone Mills. White Oak Plant, 1980-1982 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Cone Mills. Workers Union Voice, 1980-1982 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Cone Mills, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  Salisbury, NC
- Cone Mills. Tabardrey Plant, 1980-1981 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  Hawriver, NC
- Cordova Mills, 1978-1980 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  Cordova, Alabama
- Courtaulds North America, 1976-1980 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  LeMayne, Alabama
- Cranston Print, 1976-1982 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Cranston Print, 1976-1982 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  Fletcher, NC
- OSHA Cotton Dust Compliance Program, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  Employee Education & Training. Warning Signs. Record Keeping. Access to Info. OSHA Inspections. Misc.
- OSHA Cotton Dust Compliance Program, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  Federal Registrar. Company Policy. Standard Summary. Overview of Processes. Engineering Controls
- OSHA Cotton Dust Compliance Program, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  Work Practice Control. Respirator Program. Medical Surveillance
- DePorter Industries, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  Wilmington, SC
- Highland Yarn Mills, 1980-1982 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Linn-Corriher Mills, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- M. Lowenstein Co., 1978-1981 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  Rock Hill,SC
- Ludlow Textiles, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  Indianola, Mississippi
- Ludlow Textile Div. of Ludlow Corp., 1981 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Maryland Ribbon Co., 1979 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  Hagerstown, MD
- Medi-Clean, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  Rome,GA
- Meiwa Mfg., 1980 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  Charlotte,NC
- Millikin Company, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Monitor Inc, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  Chapel Hill, NC
- Monroe Print, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  Monroe, NC
- Mt. Vernon Mills, 1979-1981 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  West Columbia, SC
- Munsingwear, Inc, 1981-1982 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  Hamilton,AL
- Ludlow Textiles, 1976-1982 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Oneita Mills, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 19)
- Oneita Mills, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 20)
- Granby Dept. Carding, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 21)
- Oneita Mills, 1979-1980 (Box 3, Folder 22)
- Oneita Mills, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 23)
- Opelika Mfg. Co., 1979-1981 (Box 3, Folder 24)
- Opelika Mfg. Corp., 1981 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  March 27th
- Opelika Mfg. Co., 1981-1982 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  Phenix City, Alabama
- Owens Fiberglass, 1977-1980 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  Hunnington, PA
- Pacific Columbia Mills, 1979-1980 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  Columbia, SC
- Pickett Mills, 1981-1982 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  Highpoint, NC
- Plus Mark Co., 1980-1981 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  Greenville, TN
- Poritts & Spencer, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  Wilson, NC
- Raybestos Manhattan, 1977-1981 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  Charleston, SC
- Schlegak TN Company, 1981-1983 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  Maryville, TN
- Skyland International Corp, 1978-1982 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Agricultural. Mushroom Workers Handbook (Box 4, Folder 7)
  Spanish and English
- Dry Cleaners, 19853-1992 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Hazards by Industry Farmworkers, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Food Processing, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- ACTWU Documents., 1980 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Health Hazards in Textile Finishing Operations, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Textile Industry, 1984-1986 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Cotton Dust Standard, 1982-1983 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Cotton Dust Standard, 1981-1983 (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Cotton Dust Standard, 1981-1983 (Box 4, Folder 16)
- OSHA Complaint Forms, 1986-1990 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  200 Log & Fact Sheets
- 200 Log & Fact Sheet Continued, 1978-1995 (Box 4, Folder 18)
- OSHA Complaint Forms, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  200 Log & Record
- OSHA Statistics. Injury & Illnesses. Summary Evaluating your firm, 1978-1991 (Box 4, Folder 20)
- Byssinosis. ACTWU Economic Impact Study, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 21)
- Byssinosis. ATMI Negotiations, 1981-1983 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Byssinosis Clippings, 1969-1982 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Byssinosis. Cotton Washing, 1984-1995 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Byssinosis. Cotton Washing, 1983-1986 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Byssinosis. Cotton Washing, 1986-1995 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Byssinosis. Cotton Washing [1 of 2], 1981-1982 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Byssinosis. Cotton Washing [2 of 2], 1978-1982 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Byssinosis. Cotton Washing Process, 1983-1989 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Byssinosis. Cotton Washing Process & Toxic Data, 1978-1984 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Byssinosis. Cotton Washing Protocols, 1985-1988 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Byssinosis. Cotton Washing Protocols, 1980-1985 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Byssinosis. Cotton Washing Task Force, 1985-1989 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Byssinosis. Dust Control [1 of 2], 1972-1981 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Byssinosis. Dust Control [2 of 2], 1972-1979 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Byssinosis. Dust Control, 1983-1986 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Byssinosis Enforcement. # 1 Program Directive, 1979-1983 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Byssinosis Enforcement Project Direct, 1980-1985 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Byssinosis Enforcement, 1980-1993 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Byssinosis Enforcement, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Byssinosis. Literature [1 of 2], 1981-1984 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Byssinosis Literature, 1984-1989 (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Byssinosis Literature [1 of 2], 1969-1975 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Byssinosis Literature [2 of 2], 1969-1975 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Byssinosis Literature, 1976-1990 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Byssinosis Literature [1 of 2], 1964-1980 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Byssinosis Literature [2 of 2], 1964-1980 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Byssinosis Literature, 1969-1983 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Byssinosis Medical Surveillance, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Byssinosis. Merchant: PHD Thesis on Byssinosis Studies, 1970-1975 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Byssinosis Merchant: PHD Thesis on Byssinosis Studies (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Byssinosis Merchant: PHD Thesis on Byssinosis Studies (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Byssinosis. Ralph Nadar, 1969-1986 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Byssinosis. National Academy of Science Study, 1977-1982 (Box 7, Folder 10)
- Byssinosis. US Government. General, 1967-1976 (Box 7, Folder 11)
- Byssinosis. US Grant, 1971-1974 (Box 7, Folder 12)
- Byssinosis. U.S. Govt., 1977-1978 (Box 7, Folder 13)
- Byssinosis. US Govt., 1979-1980 (Box 7, Folder 14)
- Byssinosis. US Govt., 1979-1980 (Box 7, Folder 15)
- Byssinosis. US Govt., 1978-1981 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Byssinosis. US Govt. Attacks, 1980-1981 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Byssinosis. US Government, 1982-1985 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Byssinosis. US Government, 1983-1985 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Byssinosis. US Government, 1983-1985 (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Byssinosis. US Government, 1985-1989 (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Byssinosis. US Government, 1985-1987 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Byssinosis. Workers Comp. General, 1970-1986 (Box 8, Folder 8)
- Byssinosis Workers Comp. General, 1969-1972 (Box 8, Folder 9)
- Byssinosis Workers' Comp, 1984-1988 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  Alabama
- Byssinosis. Workers' Comp., 1981-1984 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  Georgia
- Byssinosis. Workers' Comp., 1980-1982 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  North Carolina
- Byssinosis Workers' Comp. Panel, 1979-1982 (Box 8, Folder 13)
- Byssinosis. Workers' Comp, 1980-1984 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  Virginia
- Byssinosis. Workers' Comp, 1980-1981 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  South Carolina
- Byssinosis Workers' Comp, 1981-1989 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  Tennessee
- Byssinosis Yale University. Presumptive Criteria, 1979-1982 (Box 8, Folder 17)
- ACTWU. Educational Materials on Occupational Safety & Health, 1977-1979 (Box 8, Folder 18)
- Union H & S Organizations. ACTWU-LRAC on Injuries & Illnesses, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 19)
- ACTWU Union. H & S Organizations, 1986-1987 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- ACTWU Union. H & S Organizations, 1987-1990 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Carcinogens. Acrylonitride. NCI Study, 1988-1990 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Carcinogens. Acrylonitride. NCI Study, 1989-1994 (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Carcinogens. Acrylonitride. NCI Study [1 of 2], 1984-1987 (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Carcinogens. Acrylonitride. NCI Study [2 of 2], 1987-1988 (Box 9, Folder 6)
- Carcinogens. Acrylonitride. NCI Study, 1985-1986 (Box 9, Folder 7)
- Carcinogens. Acrylonitride. NCI Study. Protocols & Data Collection, 1989-1998 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  Protocols & Data Collection
- Carcinogens. Individual Substances, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 9)
- Acrylonitrile. Carcinogens. Proposed Std., 1978 (Box 9, Folder 10)
- Carcinogens. American Cancer Society, 1983-1984 (Box 9, Folder 11)
- Asbestos. US Govt. Proposed Standard, 1984 (Box 9, Folder 12)
- Asbestos. US Govt. Proposed Standard, 1984 (Box 9, Folder 13)
- Carcinogens. BCME, 1973-1976 (Box 9, Folder 14)
- Carcinogens. BCME, 1974-1975 (Box 9, Folder 15)
- Carcinogens. BCME, 1975-1978 (Box 9, Folder 16)
- Carcinogens. BCME, 1974-1978 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Carcinogens. Benzene, 1982-1983 (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Carcinogens. Benzidine, 1972-1978 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Carcinogens. Benzidine, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Carcinogens, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Carcinogens, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 6)
- Carcinogens. Cancer Registry, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Carcinogens. General, 1973-1995 (Box 10, Folder 8)
- Carcinogens. Literature, 1975-1995 (Box 10, Folder 9)
- Carcinogens. Chloromethyl Ethers, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 10)
- Carcinogens. Chrome Pigments, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 11)
- Carcinogens. DBCP, 1983 (Box 10, Folder 12)
- Carcinogens. DCB., 1972-1989 (Box 10, Folder 13)
- Carcinogens. Dimethylformamide, 1994-1995 (Box 10, Folder 14)
- Carcinogens. DMF.IARC, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 15)
- Carcinogens. EPA, 1976-1986 (Box 10, Folder 16)
- Carcinogens. Ethylene Oxide, 1991-1993 (Box 10, Folder 17)
- Ethylene Oxide. Breast Cancer, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 18)
- Carcinogens. ETO-Court of Appeals, 1983-1986 (Box 10, Folder 19)
- Carcinogens. ETO-Final Standard [Folder 1 of 2], 1984-1994 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  Newspaper Clipping Included
- Carcinogens. ETO-Final Standard [Folder 2 of 2], 1984-1994 (Box 10, Folder 21)
- Carcinogens. ETO-Literature, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 22)
- Carcinogens. ETO-Mortality Study, 1983-1993 (Box 10, Folder 23)
- Carcinogens. ETO-NIOSH Mortality Study, 1985-1993 (Box 10, Folder 24)
- Carcinogens. Ethylene Oxide-Petitions For ETS [Folder 1 of 2], 1981-1985 (Box 10, Folder 25)
- Carcinogens. Ethylene Oxide-Petition For ETS [Folder 2 of 2], 1981-1985 (Box 10, Folder 26)
- Carcinogens. Ethylene Oxide (ETO)-Proposed Standards., 1983 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Carcinogens. ETO-Proposed Standards. Documents, 1983-1985 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- Carcinogens. ETO-Proposed Standard. House Labor Standards. Subcommittee, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Carcinogens. ETO-STEL, 1986-1988 (Box 11, Folder 4)
- Carcinogens. Ethylene Thiourea-Report, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 5)
- Carcinogens. Kepone, 1976 (Box 11, Folder 6)
- Carcinogens. Medical Surveillance, 1980-1994 (Box 11, Folder 7)
- Carcinogens. Methylene Chloride [Folder 1 of 3], 1985-1989 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  News Clipping Included
- Carcinogens. Methylene Chloride [Folder 2 of 3], 1985-1989 (Box 11, Folder 9)
- Carcinogens. Methylene Chloride [Folder 3 of 3], 1985-1989 (Box 11, Folder 10)
- Carcinogens. Methylene Chloride [Folder 1 of 4], 1986-1994 (Box 11, Folder 11)
- Carcinogens. Methylene Chloride [Folder 2 of 4], 1986-1994 (Box 11, Folder 12)
- Carcinogens. Methylene Chloride [Folder 3 of 4], 1986-1994 (Box 11, Folder 13)
- Carcinogens. Methylene Chloride [Folder 4 of 4], 1986-1994 (Box 11, Folder 14)
- Carcinogens. Methylene Chloride-CPSC, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 15)
- Carcinogens. Methylene Chloride-EPA, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 16)
- Carcinogens. Methylene Chloride-NCI Study, 1986-1996 (Box 11, Folder 17)
- Carcinogens. Methylene Chloride-Petition for ETS, 1985-1986 (Box 11, Folder 18)
- Carcinogens. MOCA, 1973-1988 (Box 11, Folder 19)
- Carcinogens. NCI, 1971-1992 (Box 11, Folder 20)
- Carcinogens. NCI-Tannery Studies, 1975-1983 (Box 11, Folder 21)
- Carcinogens. NIOSH, 1975-1994 (Box 11, Folder 22)
- Carcinogens. Nitrosamines, 1978-1989 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  Newspaper Clippings and Photocopies Included
- Carcinogens. NTP, 1982-1995 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  National Toxicology Program
- Carcinogens. Occ. Carcinogenesis, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  Conference, March
- Carcinogens. OSHA Generic Standard, 1980-1983 (Box 11, Folder 26)
- Carcinogens. OSHA Proposed Standard, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  Newspaper Clippings Included
- Carcinogens. OSHA-Proposed Standard [Folder 1 of 3], 1975-1979 (Box 12, Folder 1)
- Carcinogens. OSHA-Proposed Standard [Folder 2 of 3], 1975-1979 (Box 12, Folder 2)
- Carcinogens. OSHA-Proposed Standard [Folder 3 of 3], 1975-1979 (Box 12, Folder 3)
- Carcinogens. Perchcoroethylene [Folder 1 of 2], 1978-1990 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  Tetrachloroethylene
- Carcinogens. Perchcoroethylene [Folder 2 of 2], 1978-1990 (Box 12, Folder 5)
- Carcinogens. Perchloroethylene-ASTDR, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 6)
- Carcinogens. Perchloroethylene-Correspondence, 1981-1997 (Box 12, Folder 7)
- Carcinogens. Perc-EPA, 1986-1989 (Box 12, Folder 8)
- Carcinogens. Perchloroethylene-IFI, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 9)
- Carcinogens. Perc-Literature, 1986-1999 (Box 12, Folder 10)
- Carcinogens. Perchloroethylene-NIOSH Mortality Study, 1985-1994 (Box 12, Folder 11)
- Carcinogens. Perchloroethylene-NIOSH Study, 1970-1994 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  Individual Substances
- Carcinogens. Perchloroethylene-Perc NIOSH Study, 1976-1980 (Box 12, Folder 13)
- Carcinogens. Perchloroethylene-NTP, 1985-1989 (Box 12, Folder 14)
- Carcinogens. Perc-Petitions for Standards, 1985 (Box 12, Folder 15)
- Carcinogens. Regulatory Council, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 16)
- Carcinogens. Regulatory Council-Cancer Policy, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 17)
- Carcinogens. TDI-NCI Study (Box 12, Folder 18)
- Carcinogens. TDI-Literature, 1985-1987 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  French Included
- Carcinogens. Textile & Other Workers Covered By ACTWU, 1975-1980 (Box 12, Folder 20)
- ACTWU Distributions. Workers' Compensation, 1979-1989 (Box 12, Folder 21)
- AFL-CIO Position. Workers Comp., 1979-1994 (Box 12, Folder 22)
- AFL-CIO Position. Workers' Compensation [Folder 1 of 2], 1977-1994 (Box 12, Folder 23)
- AFL-CIO Postion. Workers' Compensation [Folder 2 of 2], 1977-1994 (Box 12, Folder 24)
- Workers Compensation. APHA Task Force, 1980-1994 (Box 12, Folder 25)
- Workers Compensation. Arbitration, 1980-1985 (Box 12, Folder 26)
- Workers Compensation. Companies, 1977-1981 (Box 12, Folder 27)
- Workers Compensation. Economic Factors, 1979-1987 (Box 12, Folder 28)
- Workers Compensation. Education, 1981-1982 (Box 12, Folder 29)
- Workers Compensation. Employee Discrimination, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 30)